Thanks for coming back.
欢迎回来
So we have a couple of cakes already.
我们已经有几个蛋糕了
But you know, can you ever have too many cakes?
那还不能拥有更多蛋糕吗？
That was a rhetorical question, the answer is obviously no.
这是一个反问 答案显然可以
So in light of this delicious fact,
所以从美味的角度来看
let's make another cake.
还要再做一个蛋糕
But we've learned from lesson one that if I make the cake,
我们在第一课已经了解到
it'll be downright ugly.
我做的蛋糕很丑
If I let a professional make it,
但如果让专业人士来做
then it'll look amazing, but there'll be no love or personality in it.
就很漂亮 但是没有爱 也没有个性
This next cake needs the love and care from
第二个蛋糕缺乏第一个蛋糕的爱与心意
the first cake and the quality of the second cake.
但第一个蛋糕又需要第二个的质量
Oh, well, hi Miriam.
哦 嗨 Miriam
Hi there.
你好
Can you tell us a little bit about what you do here in Udacity.
能告诉我们你在 Udacity 都做些什么吗?
Yeah, I work on our mentorship programs to help
哦 我在准备导师计划项目
support student learning and improve their experience.
为学生的学习提供帮助和改善他们的体验
That's really amazing, Miriam.
真的太棒啦 Miriam
You do so much for the student community,
你为学生社区做了这么多
and I know they really appreciate it.
他们一定很感激你
But I also know that you have some other hobbies as well.
我知道你还有一些其他爱好
Yeah, let's see, among other things I bake a lot for the office.
是的 你看 我还为办公室的人们烘焙糕点
And it's awesome. I mean, really,
好棒啊 我的意思是
everything she makes disappears instantly.
她能享受到的一切美好转瞬即逝 真的
Thank you so much.
非常感谢
So, I was wondering,
我妈妈的生日快到了
my mom's birthday is coming up.
所以我想
Would you mind making a cake for her?
你介不介意为她做蛋糕呢？
Oh my gosh. I would be honored.
天啊 我感到非常荣幸
That's awesome. Thanks so much, Miriam.
那就太好了 非常感谢 Miriam
She will love it.
我一定做一个让她喜欢的蛋糕
I hope so. I'll go get baking.
相信她会喜欢的 我去烤吧
Asking Miriam to bake a cake for me is just like
请求 Miriam 为我烘烤一个蛋糕就像
the new technology we'll be looking at in this lesson.
我们在本课学到的新方法一样
I'm not doing the work,
我实际上没有做任何事情
I just make the request,
仅仅只是请求
and I don't have to load some professional library like
不必加载一些专业的库 如 jQuery
jQuery because this new tool is provided right in the browser.
因为浏览器恰好提供了这个新工具
So, what is this life-changing tech?
那么改变生活的技术是什么？
Drum roll please.
请击鼓
I give you the Fetch API.
我已经给大家介绍了 Fetch API
So, yeah, the name isn't all that impressive-sounding,
的确 这个名字不是那么令人印象深刻
but Fetch really is an amazing tool that will change how you
但是 Fetch 真的是一个很好的工具
write asynchronous requests. Let's see how it works.
可以改变你编写异步请求的方式 我们现在来看看它是如何运行的